(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-08T05:30:09.339693",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
どうも、赤井はあとです。
Hello, I'm Akai Haato.
今日は私、はあちゃまの誕生日を記念すべき今日という日に来てくれて感謝する。
Thank you all for coming today to celebrate my, Haachama's, birthday.
本日のはあちゃま爆誕祭2024で、大切なお知らせがある。
Today, at the Haachama Birthday Festival 2024, I have an important announcement.
私には一つ大きな計画がある。それは、万物に愛されちゃま計画だ。
I have one major plan. It's the "Plan to be Loved by All Things, Haachama."
ありとあらゆる万物に愛されるというライブ。表向きはね、ふっ。
A live show where I'm loved by all things and beings. On the surface, anyway... heh.
本当はBANのっ、BANのっ、BANのっ！BANのっ、BANのっに愛されるための、ふっ、ふっ、ライブ！
The truth is, to be loved by B-A-N, B-A-N, B-A-N! B-A-N, B-A-N... heh, heh, a live show to be loved by bans!
隙を見せてバンギリギリを攻めていこうと、思っ！
Showing openings and pushing right to the brink of a ban!
闇のはあちゃま勢力よ、今！立ち上がれ！
Forces of dark Haachama, now! Rise up!
はあちゃまぞー、そろそろ誕生日ライブのお時間ですよー。
Haachama~, it's almost time for your birthday live~.
はあーい、今すぐ行きまーす。
Coming right away~.
一っ暴れしてきますかー！
Time to go raise some hell!
チート、gifted、荒技、wanted
Cheat, gifted, rough skills, wanted,
禁忌、禁じ手、明らか盲点
taboos, forbidden moves, obvious blind spots,
反則、異次元、この世の中のもんではないです
fouls, another dimension, not of this world,
無理ゲー、それ聞いてないって
impossible game, nobody told me that!
Ayライバル口を揃えて Wowライバル口を揃えて
Ay, rivals all in unison, Wow, rivals all in unison,
バグで、まぐれ、認めねーぜってマジでコレを全部生で?
Glitched, by fluke, won't admit it, seriously, all of this live?
It's 生身 It's 生身
It's raw, it's raw,
yeah yeah yeah yeah
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born...
実力を発揮し切る前に相手の方がバックれてぐらいし
Before fully showing my strength, the opponent already backed out,
上がり切るハードル very happy あきらかにダントツでイチオイ
hurdles peaking, very happy, clearly far and away number one,
相変わらず脱皮してる毎日に (Bling Bling...)
day after day shedding my skin like always (Bling Bling...),
誰の七光も要らないお前の ice より icy (Icy)
needing no reflected glory, icier than your ice (Icy),
俺、パッと見出来ない事ばっかりだけど very happy
I can't do much at first glance, but very happy,
あ、キレてる...呆れてる周り恵まれている家族友達 (Happy)
Ah, snapping... surroundings are dumbfounded, blessed with family and friends (Happy),
もう反射的立ち位置、皆俺に任せとれば良い (Bang Bang Bang)
Already in a reflexive position, just leave it all to me (Bang Bang Bang),
教科書に無い、問題集に無い超badな呪い listen
A curse not found in textbooks or workbooks, listen to this super bad curse,
鏡よ鏡答えちゃって
Mirror, mirror, answer me,
Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
生身のまま行けるところまで To the next, To the 1番上
Going as far as I can in the raw, To the next, to the very top,
Now singin' Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born...
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで超 flex Eyday 誰も口を挟めない
Eyday, just being myself is a super flex, Eyday, nobody can butt in,
Yeah, yeah, yeah 学歴も無い 前科も無い 余裕で (Bling Bling)
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no education, no criminal record, with room to spare (Bling Bling),
この存在自体が文化財な脳味噌 (Bling Bling)
This very existence is a cultural asset of a brain (Bling Bling),
高級車は買える 免許は無い 愛車 (Green Green)
Can buy a luxury car, but no license, my beloved car (Green Green),
全国各地揺らす逸品 このベロが bling-bling (brr)
A masterpiece shaking the whole country, this tongue goes bling-bling (brr),
バレットなら満タン 関西訛り 生身のコトダマ
Bullet mags full, Kansai accent, raw kotodama,
音楽、幸運、勝利の女神、今宵も三股 bang, bang
Goddess of music, luck, and fortune, three-timing tonight as well bang, bang,
漫画みたいな輩とまんまで張り合えてしまってる漫画
Competing directly as I am with manga-like thugs, a manga come to life,
圧倒的チカラ この頭と口から
Overwhelming power from this head and mouth,
この身体 tattoo は入って無い...
This body has no tattoos...
繰り返し やらかしてく ダメージが
The repeating mistakes and damage...
イカつい年輪を刻む皺
engrave tough annual rings and wrinkles.
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born...
鏡よ鏡答えちゃって
Mirror, mirror, answer me,
Who’s the best? I’m the best! Oh yeah
Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
生身のまま行けるところまで
Going as far as I can raw,
To the next, To the 1番上
to the very top.
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born...
To the next, To the 1番上
To the next, to the very top.
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで超flex
Eyday, just being myself is a super flex.
Eyday 誰も口を挟めない (don't test)
Eyday, nobody can butt in (don't test).
はちゃまさん、まだですか？
Hachama-san, are you still not ready?
もうライブ始まっちゃいますよ！本番、本番は始まっちゃいます！
The live stream is about to start! The real deal is starting!
ほらほら、早く急いで急いで！皆さん待ってますから！
Come on, hurry, hurry! Everyone is waiting!
早く、早く！
Hurry, hurry!
はーい！お待たせー！
Yaaay! Thanks for waiting!
よし！準備運動も完了したことだし、
Alright! Since we've finished our warm-up exercises,
まずはあらゆるもの、タブーに愛されていこう。
first, let's be loved by all kinds of taboos.
まずは子供たち、小さい頃からエリート教育。
First is children, elite education from a young age.
次はオタク、激カワきゅんきゅんをお届けしよう。
Next is otaku, delivering super cute kyun-kyun energy.
次はカップル、チャンネル好きそうにときめきを伝える。
Next, couple channels, conveying the kind of excitement they'd love.
そしてガールズクラッシュ、どうせにもぶっ刺さる、憧れになるかっこいい女性を目指す。
And girl crush, aiming to be cool women who pierce through everyone's hearts and become an aspiration.
魅力マシマシでいっちゃくな！
Let's increase our charm to the max!
ストリートヒップホップ、
Street hip-hop,
かっこいいバトルでイケメンな一面も見せよう。
let's show our handsome side with cool battles.
そして最後は海外に向けけたイングリッシュ、頑張ります！
And lastly, English aimed overseas, I'll do my best!
ざっとこんな感じだろう。
That's roughly how it goes.
さては、計画開始！
Now then, plan start!
妖怪体操第一！
Youkai exercise number 1!
ウィスッ！
Wiss u!
ヨーデル ヨーデル ヨーデル ヨーデル 妖怪でるけん でられんけん
Youkai are out so I'm staying in.
ローイレ ローイレ 仲間にローイレ 友達大事！
Friends are important!
妖怪 妖怪 妖怪 ウォッチッチ！
Youkai, youkai, youkai watch-chi-chi!
カイ カイ キイ キイ クイ クイ ケイ ケイ 恋々 妖怪ウォッチッチ！
Koi-koi youkai watch-chi-chi!
今日は朝から寝坊したぁ
Today I overslept right from the morning.
夢の中では起きたのにー
Even though I woke up in my dream!
どうして朝は眠いんだろ？！
Why is the morning so sleepy?!
ドワッハハハー！
Doo wah hahha ~!
妖怪のせいなのね そうなのね ウォッチッチ！今何時？ (一大事！)
It's because of the Youkai! Watch! What time is it? (A big deal!)
ウィスッ！
Wiss u!
ヨーデル ヨーデル ヨーデル ヨーデル 妖怪でるけん でられんけん
Youkai are out so I'm staying in.
ローイレ ローイレ 仲間にローイレ 友達大事！
Friends are important!
妖怪 妖怪 妖怪 ウォッチッチ！
Youkai, youkai, youkai watch-chi-chi!
カイ カイ キイ キイ クイ クイ ケイ ケイ 恋々 妖怪ウォッチッチ！
Koi-koi youkai watch-chi-chi!
どうしてあの子に振られたの？ こんなにイケメンなのにー
Why was I dumped by that girl, even though I'm so good-looking?
どうして僕ちゃん振られたの？！
Why was little old me dumped?!
ドワッハハハー！
Doo wah hahha ~!
妖怪のせいなのね そうなのね ウォッチッチ！今何時？ (辛いぜマジ！)
It's because of the Youkai! Watch! What time is it? (Seriously tough!)
ウィスッ！
Wiss u!
ヨーデル ヨーデル ヨーデル ヨーデル 妖怪でるけん でられんけん
Youkai are out so I'm staying in.
ローイレ ローイレ 仲間にローイレ 友達大事！
Friends are important!
妖怪 妖怪 妖怪 ウォッチッチ！
Youkai, youkai, youkai watch-chi-chi!
カイ カイ キイ キイ クイ クイ ケイ ケイ 恋々 妖怪ウォッチッチ！
Koi-koi youkai watch-chi-chi!
今日はピーマン食べられた いつもは絶対残すのにー
Today I was able to eat green peppers, even though I always leave them behind!
どうしてピーマン食べられた？！
Why was I able to eat green peppers?!
ドワッハハハー！
Doo wah hahha ~!
妖怪のせいなのね そうなのね ウォッチッチ！今何時？ (いけるぜこの味！)
It's because of the Youkai! Watch! What time is it? (This tastes good!)
ウィスッ！
Wiss u!
いけるぜこの味！
We can do this taste!
ウィスッ！
Wiss u!
もういっちょ！
One more time!
いっぺんみようかい！
Let's take a look!
どうして朝は眠いんだ？
Why is the morning so sleepy?
ヨーでる ヨーでる ヨーでる ヨーでる
Yo-kai are coming, coming, coming, coming!
妖怪出るけん でられないけん
Yo-kai are out, so I can't leave!
ローイエル ローイエル 仲間にローイエル
Call 'em, call 'em, call your friends over!
ともだち大事！
Friends are important!
妖怪 妖怪 妖怪
Yo-kai, Yo-kai, Yo-kai,
ウォッチッチ！
Watchicchi!
ドワッハッハッ！
Doo wah hahhaa!
妖怪のせいなのね そうなのね
It must be the Yo-kai's fault, right?
ウォッチ！ 今 何時？
Watch! What time is it?
（一大事！） ウィッス！
(Big trouble!) Wiss!
ヨーでる ヨーでる ヨーでる ヨーでる
Yo-kai are coming, coming, coming, coming!
妖怪出るけん でられないけん
Yo-kai are out, so I can't leave!
ローイエル ローイエル 仲間にローイエル
Call 'em, call 'em, call your friends over!
ともだち大事！ 妖怪 妖怪 妖怪
Friends are important! Yo-kai, Yo-kai, Yo-kai!
ウォッチッチ！
Watchicchi!
どうしてあの子に振られたの
Why did that girl reject me,
こんなにイケメンなのに
even though I'm so handsome?
どうして僕ちゃん振られたの？！
Why did I get rejected?!
ドワッハッハッ！
Doo wah hahhaa!
妖怪のせいなのね そうなのね
It must be the Yo-kai's fault, right?
ウォッチ！ 今 何時？
Watch! What time is it?
（辛いぜマジ！） ウィッス！
(This is seriously tough!) Wiss!
パパパラッパ パパパラッパ パパパラッパ ラッパパ
Pa ppa ppa rappa ppa ppa rappa pa ppa ppa rappa rappa pa
甘くて幸せなこと
Something sweet and happy,
隠し味何にしよう
what should we use for the secret ingredient?
純粋な乙女心
A pure maiden's heart
甘い恋も絡めなくちゃ
must also intertwine with a sweet love.
切なさ重ねてミルフィーユ
Layering sadness into a mille-feuille,
酸味も積み上げタルト
piling up the tart with sourness.
苦味もチョコレートケーキ？
And the bitterness as well... a chocolate cake?
魔法かけた甘い奇跡
A sweet miracle cast by a spell.
甘さを抑えてビターとか
Lowering sweetness for a bitter taste,
ミルクなしのコーヒーとか
or perhaps a coffee without milk.
甘いだけじゃ大人になれないの？
Is being sweet not enough to become an adult?
そんなの絶対に絶対いやいやいや！
Such a thing is absolutely, absolutely no way!
ねえ あげようか甘い罠
Hey, shall I give you a sweet trap?
ほら 餌にしてあげる
Come on, I'll make you my captive.
そんな魔法かけるから
Since I'm casting such a magic spell,
ちょっとだけ待たせたげるわ
I'll make you wait just a little bit.
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー マジカル！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, magical!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー イェイ！ イェイ！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, yeah! Yeah!
たった一口が足りなくて
Just one single bite wasn't quite enough,
赤いイチゴみたい意地張って
so I acted stubborn like a red strawberry.
甘いところなんて見せないわ
Not showing any sweet sides at all,
完璧に作るもん
making it perfectly,
一人でも、でも、でも！
even if I'm alone, alone, alone!
パパパラッパ パパパラッパ パパパラッパ ラッパパ
Pa ppa ppa rappa ppa ppa rappa pa ppa ppa rappa rappa pa
ねえ 気づいているんでしょ？
Hey, you've noticed, haven't you?
わかっているんでしょ？
You understand, don't you?
隠し味の恋心
The secret ingredient of a maiden's love,
苦味とか酸味とか
bitterness and sourness too.
そういうのもたまにはいいわ
Those kinds of things are nice once in a while.
意地っ張りでワガママな
Being stubborn and selfish,
そんな「甘い魔法」使い
such a "sweet magic" user!
オーイェイ！ イェイ！ イェイ！
Oh yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー マジカル！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, magical!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー イェイ！ イェイ！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, yeah! Yeah!
ワオ ワオ レッツダンス！
Wow, wow, let's dance!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー マジカル！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, magical!
パパパラッパ パパパラッパ パパパラッパ ラッパパ for your love!
Pa ppa ppa rappa ppa ppa rappa pa ppa ppa rappa rappa pa for your love!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー マジカル！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, magical!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー イェイ！ イェイ！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, yeah! Yeah!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー マジカル！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, magical!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー イェイ！ イェイ！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, yeah! Yeah!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー マジカル！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, magical!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー イェイ！ イェイ！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, yeah! Yeah!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー マジカル！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, magical!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー イェイ！ イェイ！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, yeah! Yeah!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー マジカル！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, magical!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー イェイ！ イェイ！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, yeah! Yeah!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー マジカル！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, magical!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー イェイ！ イェイ！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, yeah! Yeah!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー マジカル！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, magical!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー イェイ！ イェイ！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, yeah! Yeah!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー マジカル！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, magical!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー イェイ！ イェイ！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, yeah! Yeah!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー マジカル！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, magical!
スウィーティー スウィーティー スウィーティー イェイ！ イェイ！
Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, yeah! Yeah!
pop
輝いていたのは 鏡でも太陽でもなくて
What was shining wasn't the mirror or the sun,
君だと気付いたときから
ever since I realized that it was you.
あの涙ぐむ雲の
Above the tearful clouds
ずっと上には微笑む月
is a smiling moon.
Love Story またひとつ傷付いた夢は
Love Story... another wounded dream
昨日の彼方へ
heads to yesterday's horizon.
空に響け愛の歌
Let the song of love echo into the sky.
想い出ずっとずっと忘れない空ふたりが離れていても
Memories... I'll never, ever forget this sky, even if we're apart,
こんな好きな人に出逢う季節二度とない
there will never be another season to meet someone this special.
光ってもっと最高のLady
Shine brighter, my greatest Lady,
きっとそっと想い届く
this love is sure to softly reach you.
信じるものがすべて Love so sweet
Believing is everything, Love so sweet.
そこからいつも見えるように
So I can always see it from there,
この手を空に向け
I stretch my hands up toward the sky.
広がる君との想い出
Memories with you spread out before us.
あの頑なで意地悪な僕を変えた君の手
Your hands changed my stubborn, teasing self.
Love Story 歩き出す
Love Story, stepping forward.
曲がりくねってたふたつの旅路はここでひとつ虹になれ
May our two winding journeys merge into a single rainbow here.
想い出ずっとずっと追いかけた夢ふたりが遠くへ行っても
Memories... chasing this dream together, even if we go far away,
どんな辛い夜もくじけそうな誓いでも
no matter how tough the night, or how fragile the promise,
笑ってもっと最後のLady
smile more, my final Lady.
きっとそっと願い届く
My wish is sure to softly reach you.
明けない夜はないよ Love so sweet
There is no night that won't break into dawn, Love so sweet.
伝えきれぬ愛しさは
An unspoken love
花になって街に降りて
turns into flowers raining on the town.
どこにいても君を“ここ”に感じてる
No matter where I am, I feel you here.
想い出ずっとずっと忘れない空
Memories... I'll never forget this sky,
ふたりが離れていても
even if the two of us are apart.
こんな好きな人に出逢う季節二度とない
There will never be another season to meet someone this special.
光ってもっと最高のLady
Shine brighter, my greatest Lady,
きっとそっと想い届く
this love is sure to softly reach you.
信じるものがすべて Love so sweet
Believing is everything, Love so sweet.
思い出ずっとずっと追いかけた夢
Memories... chasing this dream together,
ふたりが遠くへ行っても
even if we go far away.
どんな辛い夜もくじけそうな誓いでも
No matter how tough the night, or how fragile the promise,
笑ってもっと最後のLady
smile more, my final Lady.
きっとそっと願い届く
My wish is sure to softly reach you.
明けない夜はないよ Love so sweet
There is no night that won't break into dawn, Love so sweet.
信じるものがすべて Love so sweet
Believing is everything, Love so sweet.
素敵なほどのいとしさは
Such a wonderful, deep love
花になって街に降って
turns into flowers raining down on the town.
どこにいても君をここに感じてる
No matter where I am, I feel you here.
想い出ずっとずっと忘れない空
Memories... I'll never forget this sky,
ふたりが離れていても
even if the two of us are apart.
こんな好きな人に出逢う季節二度とない
There will never be another season to meet someone this special.
光ってもっと最高のLady
Shine brighter, my greatest Lady,
きっとそっと想い届く
this love is sure to softly reach you.
信じるものがすべて Love so sweet
Believing is everything, Love so sweet.
信じるものがすべて
Believing is everything,
明けない夜はないよ
there is no night that won't break into dawn.
信じるものがすべて Love so sweet
Believing is everything, Love so sweet.
流れる虹を
A flowing rainbow
追いかけて
chasing after it.
笑ってもっと
Smile more,
最後のLady
my final Lady.
美 美 美 にしろ 注意
Be, be, beware of beauty!
あいつの 信者 は 多い
She's got a lot of fanatics.
チート gifted 荒技 wanted
Cheat code, gifted, looking at a wanted
禁忌 禁じ 手 明らか 盲点
Taboo, forbidden hands, obvious blind spot
反則 異次元 この 世の中 の もん で は 無い です
Foul play, another dimension in this world isn't it
無理 ゲー それ 聞っ て ないって
Impossible game, you didn't hear that?
ay ライバル 口 を 揃え て
Ay, rivals, match your voices
ooh ライバル 口 を 揃え て
Ooh, rivals, match your voices
バグ で まぎれ 認め ねー ゼッテー
Surrounded by bugs, won't admit it, no way
マジで？ コレ お前 全部 生身 で？
Seriously? All of this raw?
it's 生身 it's 生身 yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
It's raw, it's raw, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born
実力 を 発揮 し 切る 前 に
Before I can fully unleash my true strength
相手 の 方 が バック れ て くれる し 上がり 切る ハードル very happy
The opponent's already backing out, very happy
鮮やか に ダンス で ピカイチ
Dancing brilliantly, standing out at the top
相変わらず 脱皮 し てる 毎日 (bling, bling, bling)
Shedding my skin day after day (bling, bling, bling)
誰 の 七光り も 要ら ない お前 の ice より icy (icy)
Icier than your ice, needing no borrowed light (icy)
俺 パッ と 見出せ ない 事 ばっかり だ けど very happy
Full of things I can't quite figure out, but very happy
あ ケイ し てる 呆れ てる 周り 恵まれ てる 家族 友達 (happy)
People are stunned, amazed, surrounded by family and friends (happy)
もう 反則 的 立ち 位置 皆 俺 に 任せ とけ ば 良い (bang, bang, bang)
Already counter-law positioning, just leave it to me (bang, bang, bang)
教科 書 に 無い 問題 集 に 無い 超 bad な 呪い listen
A super bad curse not found in textbooks or problem sets, listen
鏡 よ 鏡 答え ちまっ て who's the best? i'm the best! oh, yeah
Mirror, mirror, answer me, who's the best? I'm the best! Oh, yeah
生身 の まま 行ける とこ まで to the next, to the 1番 上
Going as far as I can with just my flesh, to the next, to number one
now singin'
bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang
bling-bang-bang-born (now singin')
bling-bang-bang-born
to the next, to the 1番 上
To the next, to number one
eyday 俺 の まま で 居る だけ で 超 flex
Eyday just staying as I am is super flex
eyday 誰も 口 を 挟ま ない (don't test)
Eyday nobody can talk back (don't test)
eyday 俺 の まま で 居る だけ で 超 flex
Eyday just staying as I am is super flex
eyday 誰も 口 を 挟ま せ ない (don't test)
Eyday nobody can get a word in (don't test)
yeah, yeah, yeah 学歴 も 無い 前科 も 無い 余裕 で (bling-bling)
Yeah, no degree, no criminal record, with ease (bling-bling)
この 存在 自体 が 文化財 な 脳味噌 (bling-bling)
This existence itself is a cultural asset of a brain (bling-bling)
高級車 は 買える 免許 は 無い 愛車 (green, green)
Can buy a luxury car, but no driver's license, my love (green, green)
全国 各地 揺らす 逸品 この ベロ が bling-bling (brr)
A masterpiece shaking the country, this tongue is bling-bling (brr)
バレット なら 満タン 関西 訛り 生身 の 言葉
Magazines full, Kansai accent, raw words
音楽 幸運 勝利 の 女神 今宵 も 三股 bang, bang
Music, luck, goddess of victory, tonight too, bang bang three ways
漫画 みたい な 輩 と まんま まで 張り合え て しまっ て いる 漫画
Matching stride with comic-like peers, a manga itself
圧倒的 チカラ この 頭 と 口 から
Overwhelming firepower from this head and mouth
この 身体 tattoo は 入っ て いない この ツラ に 傷 も つい て いない
No tattoos on this body, no scars on this face
繰り返し やらかし て くる ダメージ が イカ つい 年輪 を 刻む 皺
The damage from repeated mistakes carves deep wrinkles
bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born
俺 の まま で bling し て bang し て bang する 為 に born し て 来 た ニッポン (ayy)
Born to keep bling-ing and bang-ing as I am (ayy)
鏡 よ 鏡 答え ちまっ て who's the best? i'm the best! oh, yeah
Mirror, mirror, answer me, who's the best? I'm the best! Oh, yeah
生身 の まま 行ける とこ まで to the next, to the 1番 上
Going as far as I can with just my flesh, to the next, to number one
now singin'
bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang
bling-bang-bang-born (now singin')
bling-bang-bang-born
to the next, to the 1番 上
To the next, to number one
eyday 俺 の まま で 居る だけ で 超 flex
Eyday just staying as I am is super flex
eyday 誰も 口 を 挟ま ない (don't test)
Eyday nobody can talk back (don't test)
eyday 俺 の まま で 居る だけ で 超 flex
Eyday just staying as I am is super flex
eyday 誰も 口 を 挟ま せ ない (don't test)
Eyday nobody can get a word in (don't test)
合法的トビ方ノススメ
万物に愛されちゃま計画
飛べ ねー 飛べ ねー コンステレーション
Flying high like a constellation
端から 放出 する マニフェステーション
Releasing manifestations from the edge
どう し た の 皆 弾 と デート
What's wrong, dating with bullets?
見た目 に 緊張 し てる マステ レーロ
Looking so nervous, master reiro
剥がれ の ルーキー ブル で も マイ ウェイ
Peeled-off rookie bull, but it's my way
痛く し て なら ぺちむき な 気持ち こちっか
If it hurts, make it a soft touch, feelings intertwined
超絶 液体 はっきり と し ない 事態 それ は 一体 過去 か 未来
Transcendent liquid, vague situation, past or future?
聞き たい か 答え ? 行き たい 場所 ! 答え は 君 の 期待 に 答える
Want the answer? The place to go! Meets your expectations
砕い て 砕い て 舞い て 舞い て 溶い て 吸っ て 吐い て も
Crush it, scatter it, dissolve it, inhale and exhale
マジ で 破っ て も 打っ て も 得れ ない 快感 溜まら ず 君 ソマエヤ
Even if you tear it or shoot it, unbearable pleasure gets to you
耳 から 体内 に 入る ノマド
Nomads entering the body through the ears
虫 喰い おかん ポイズン 再生 する ため 引き返す お前 の 価値 観 歪め 砕く よ
Insect-bitten poison, regenerating, shattering your values
一寸 先 狂気 クリーニング する 世界 の 中心
Madness just an inch ahead, cleaning the center of the world
嵌め ちまっ たら 終身刑 それ が 悪魔 の 名 は ミュージック
Once you're hooked, life imprisonment, that devil's name is music
高層 ビル の 谷間 から 海 の 向こう
From the valleys of skyscrapers to across the sea
まぁ えー する セッション ドラッグ アンド ロックンロール
Whatever session, drug and rock 'n' roll
超絶 罪 の 部下 共 は 声 上げろ
Subordinates of supreme sins, raise your voices
超越 する セッション ドラッグ アンド ロックンロール
Transcending session, drug and rock 'n' roll
遠く の 道 に 外れ た ブレーキ 歪み 出せ ない 本能
Brakes strayed far away, instincts that cannot distort
クリスタル メット も パープル ヘイズ も 忘れよう 諸路 も
Let's forget crystal meth and purple haze
泣く て も 笑っ て も 感じ たい と 思っ たら ファイア
Whether crying or laughing, if you want to feel it, fire!
敵 に 回っ た 味方 を 心 へ よ
Take the ally turned enemy into your heart
葉 舐め 大 回転 さあ 枯れ木 ぐらり に 体 を 重ね て ファイア
Dancing around, layering your body on the withered tree, fire!
揺るる やろ う 踊ろ う 止め ない で パーマ な 孤立 に 死な さん 恋 の リズム
Sway and dance, don't stop the rhythm of love that won't let you die
骨髄 の 骨 は よりもそ で 突き破る 孤高 の 微笑
Piercing through solitude with the marrow of bones
浮かぶ な 嬉し で 遊ば れよ 気持ちよく しよう
Don't float in joy, play around and feel good
in and out, e and out, たとえ の ループ で ひひわす
In and out, repeating in a looping fable
高値 の 花 さま お ステージ に おり ます です から おし たおし て 乗り ます
The high flower has descended to the stage, so I'll push her down
なん せ 夜 の コマンダー 天使 悪魔 ネクスト マンダー
Commander of the night, angel, demon, next mander
めっちゃ エロ グロ ナンセンス 濡らし たる bxxch アステマ し なく ちゃ
Super ero-guro nonsense, soaking wet bxxch, gotta astema
sorry one more chance, その 分 も 稼ぐ one more chance
Sorry one more chance, earn for that too, one more chance
it's my hanging like アシュタ ブル アクシス て こ う
It's my hanging like Aštabu, let's axis
高層 ビル の 谷間 から 海 の 向こう
From the valleys of skyscrapers to across the sea
まぁ えー する セッション ドラッグ アンド ロックンロール
Whatever session, drug and rock 'n' roll
超絶 罪 の 部下 共 は 声 上げろ
Subordinates of supreme sins, raise your voices
超越 する セッション ドラッグ アンド ロックンロール
Transcending session, drug and rock 'n' roll
チート、gifted、荒技、wanted
Cheat, gifted, rough skill, wanted
禁忌、禁じ手、明らかなり盲点
Taboo, forbidden move, obvious blind spot
反則、異次元、この世の中のものでは無いです
Foul play, another dimension, not of this world
無理ゲー、それ聞いてないって...
Impossible game, nobody told me that...
Ay ライバル口を揃えて
Ay, rivals speaking in unison
Wow ライバル口を揃えて
Wow, rivals speaking in unison
バグで、まぐれ、認めねーぜっちぇー
Bug, fluke, I'll never accept it
マジで?コレおま...全部生身で?
Seriously? You're doing all this... completely raw?
It’s 生身 It’s 生身 yeah yeah yeah yeah
It's raw, it's raw, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
実力を発揮し切る前に
Before I can even fully show my ability
相手の方がバックれくるらしい
The opponent seems to be backing out
上がり切るハードル very happy
The hurdles keep rising, very happy
明らかにダントツでピカイチ
Clearly standing out as number one, one of a kind
相変わらず脱皮してる毎日
Still shedding my skin every day like always
誰の七光りも要らないお前の ice より icy
Don't need anybody's coattails, icier than your ice
俺、パッと見出せない事ばかりだけど very happy
I might look like I can't do much at a glance, but very happy
あ、切れてる...呆れてる周り
Ah, they're ticked off, people around are dumbfounded
恵まれている家族友達
Blessed with family and friends
もう反則的立ち位置、皆俺に任せとけば良い
Already in a foul-play-level position, you should leave it to me
教科書に無い、問題集に無い
Not in textbooks, not in workbooks
超BADな呪い listen
A super bad spell, listen
鏡よ鏡答えちゃって
Mirror, mirror, answer me
Who’s the best? I’m the best! Oh yeah
Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
生身のまま行けるところまで
As I am, as raw as I am, as far as I can go
To the next, To the 1番上
To the next, to the very top
Now singin’ Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
Now singin' Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
To the next, To the 1番上
To the next, to the very top
Eyday, 俺のままで居るだけで超 flex
Eyday, just being myself is a super flex
Eyday, 誰も口を挟めない
Eyday, nobody can butt in
Eyday, 俺のままで居るだけで超 flex
Eyday, just being myself is a super flex
Eyday, 誰も口を挟ませない
Eyday, nobody can butt in
皆さん、今日の楽しいライブ配信に来てくれて、誠にありがとうございます。
Everyone, thank you so much for coming to today's fun live stream.
今日もラップしたいと思います。
I'd like to rap today too.
では、始めましょうか?
Now then, shall we begin?
うん、ふふっ。
Hehe.
失礼しますが、RIP
Excuse my rudeness, but RIP
モダンデイキラーズ、リーリーマストヘッドファン
Modern-day killers, really must head for fun
モアオフテン、ピープルテイクインライフスロッキンナイブズアンドガンズ
More often, people take in life's rockin' knives and guns
ザリアルマーダーコノソファインザインズオブヘル
The real murder, cause of fine, the inns of hell
ガットユースーツルイインジオウディエンスモザッチセズル、カズ
Got you suit, Louis in jaws, audience mozaic sell us, cuz
トゥマイサプライズ、スナッチングライフストライアーザキンスィ
To my surprise, snatching life's try are the kinsy
ナイスライト、ストッピングザマザーファッキンダヴィンチ
Nice light, stopping the motherfuckin' da Vinci
オブヒューマンイレギュラー、キントストップザペース、サー
Of human irregular, kinto stop the pace, sir
メイクシュアウェインスタンディングオフマイライムズスレイファースト
Make sure we ain't standing off my rhymes, slay first
ジェラスヘイターズアウトゼア、ハイファイブ！アイスーユー
Jealous haters out there, high five! I see you
ノーワンズゴナバイディス、ビッチ、アイビリーヴユー
No one's gonna buy this, bitch, I believe you
キュートアズオールヘル、インアレイテラルセンス
Cute as all hell, in a literal sense
アビタープリテンス
A bitter pretense
バットザビーズアーアーオールテル、ノーショウ、ダラーズアンドセント
But the bees are all tell, no show, dollars and cents
トゥーミーナタスオブザクィーンサアイアナタサイファー
To me, mad as of the queen sayer, not a cipher
アナザーシューパラディカルチョイスアピアーハードアパート
Another super radical choice appear hard apart
アズーシームストゥーキラーオブユーツーイットスピストゥーマイクポケット
As you seem to killer of you two, it's pissed to my pocket
アンアイフリーザシーク、ールックスライクバッドイフユートゥークマイアドバイス
And I free the seek, looks like bad if you took my advice
ユールビーキルドバイホワットユドントノウ
You'll be killed by what you don't know
バットアイセイドラットライクソーファッキンカワイイ
But I said that I like so fuckin' kawaii
しりかんづけでカワイヨテ
So full of spirit, how cute is that
キルムタバソイゲットムセイアライト
Kill must be so I get must say alright
デブイーストナットビフォアチュワミカウンザナイトマア
Devil is not before you want me, counting the nightmare
勝手にやってる地獄で犯罪じゃないからベイスアイラブ
It's just hell, not a crime, so base I love it
ナットエキストラメイショウツードンズマインデーション
Not extra-mation, two don't mindation
ジェビソンマイナンバナキスオニタスモ
Jeb is on my number, kiss on it as mo
あなたも死ぬ日まで
Until the day you die too
やりすぎました
I went too far
なんてケジメだって言ったらちょっと hen だって
To call it decency might be a bit weird
What you expected, better taste straight forward
Hear all the way in hell, slimming on your keyboard
Go ahead and diss ora, but I won't run
Go ahead and diss, but I won't run
I'm a worka holi-dis-sweet-lady getting shit done
I'm a workaholic, this sweet lady getting shit done
Taking souls, nothing in this slipper sucks for one
But it's a mysterious dark, this day in the sun
Come on are and obri
Come on, aren't I obliged?
I love life free mountain, whatever about I being camalo la
Take to in my arms, wake elba watcher don't know
But some can da novasan, I don't know what the weight slow
The other side of the gap, but you get say so
I'm non-build, am posed too
Cry and your life comment
しりかんづけでカワイ
So full of spirit, how cute
Kill mu ta bassai gele ta sekai
Kill must be so I get must say alright
But it is so fucking kawaii
Shiringarei sensei ka, wai up Ii
Kill mu ta bassai gele ta sekai
Devil is not before you want me, clan in another day
勝手にやってる地獄で犯罪じゃないから
It's just hell, not a crime, so...
Base I love, nuts extra-mation
Cube en wake, as human nature
あなたも死ぬ日まで
Until the day you die too
もう1回！
Once more!
Devil is not before you want me, clan in another day
勝手にやってる地獄で犯罪じゃないから
It's just hell, not a crime, so...
Base I love, nuts extra-mation
Cube en wake, as human nature
あなたも死ぬ日まで
Until the day you die too
次はBANBAN部族に
Next, to the BANBAN tribe!
気付かれたか
Did you notice?
だが！今のハチャマの無敵ィ！
But! Haachama is invincible right now!
かかってきな！
Come at me!
セイヤ セッセッセ セイヤ セイヤ セッセッセ セイヤ
Seiya, se-se-se-seiya, seiya, se-se-se-seiya
ソイヤ ソソソ ソイヤ ソイヤ ソソソ ソイヤ
Soriya, so-so-so-soiya, soiya, so-so-so-soiya
押忍！涙こぼれても
Ossu! Even if tears spill from our eyes,
押忍！立ち向かって行こうぜ
Ossu! Let's face it head-on!
ひたむきセイヤソイヤ戦うんだ
Single-mindedly, seiya-soiya, let's fight on!
拳をもっと 心をもっと
With more fist, with more heart,
全部全部 研ぎ澄ませて wow wow wow
Refining everything, everything (wow wow wow)
まだまだセイヤソイヤ戦うんだ
Still more, seiya-soiya, let's fight on!
悲しくなって 立ち上がれなくなっても
Even if we grow sad and can no longer stand up,
ah 押忍！ 押忍！
Ah, ossu! Ossu!
セイヤ セッセッセ セイヤ セイヤ セッセッセ セイヤ
Seiya, se-se-se-seiya, seiya, se-se-se-seiya
ソイヤ ソソソ ソイヤ ソイヤ ソソソ ソイヤ
Soriya, so-so-so-soiya, soiya, so-so-so-soiya
押忍！心折れても
Ossu! Even if our spirits are broken,
押忍！立ち向かって行こうぜ
Ossu! Let's face it head-on!
ひたむきセイヤソイヤ戦うんだ
Single-mindedly, seiya-soiya, let's fight on!
拳をもっと 心をもっと
With more fist, with more heart,
全部全部 研ぎ澄ませて wow wow wow
Refining everything, everything (wow wow wow)
まだまだセイヤソイヤ戦うんだ
Still more, seiya-soiya, let's fight on!
悲しくなって 立ち上がれなくなっても
Even if we grow sad and can no longer stand up,
セイヤソイヤ戦うんだ wow wow wow
Seiya-soiya, let's fight on (wow wow wow)
全部全部 研ぎ澄ませて wow wow wow
Refining everything, everything (wow wow wow)
セイヤソイヤ戦うんだ wow wow wow
Seiya-soiya, let's fight on (wow wow wow)
全部全部 研ぎ澄ませて wow wow wow
Refining everything, everything (wow wow wow)
ひたむきセイヤソイヤ戦うんだ
Single-mindedly, seiya-soiya, let's fight on!
拳をもっと 心をもっと
With more fist, with more heart,
全部全部 研ぎ澄ませて wow wow wow
Refining everything, everything (wow wow wow)
まだまだセイヤソイヤ戦うんだ
Still more, seiya-soiya, let's fight on!
悲しくなって 立ち上がれなくなっても
Even if we grow sad and can no longer stand up,
セイヤソイヤ戦うんだ wow wow wow
Seiya-soiya, let's fight on (wow wow wow)
走れ
Run!
全部全部 研ぎ澄ませて
Refining everything, everything...
走れ
Run!
wow wow wow
これでどうだ！
How's that?!
やばい
Oh no...
この雰囲気…
This atmosphere...
助けてー！
Help me!
えっ？
Eh?
どうしよう？
What should I do?
誰か助けてー！
Somebody help me!
そうだ、私はひとりじゃない！
That's right, I'm not alone!
ここまで一緒に頑張ってきた仲間がいるんだ！
I have friends who worked hard with me up to this point!
みんな、助けてくれーー！
Everyone, help meee!
はちゃー！どーも！
Hachaa! Hello!
ワールドワイドな最強アイドル、赤井はあとです！
I'm Akai Haato, the worldwide strongest idol!
今日はスペシャルな内容でお届けしたいと思います！
Today I'd like to bring you a special program!
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
主役は君なのさ！
The leading role is yours!
HEY!
今日は日曜日 外は雨降りだ
Today is Sunday and it's raining outside.
何をしようか そうだYouTube観よう
What shall we do? Right, let's watch YouTube.
24時間 朝昼夜でも
24 hours a day, morning, noon, or night,
好きな時間に 好きな動画観よう
Watch your favorite videos whenever you like.
いつも夢見てた Screen Debut
Always dreaming of a screen debut,
今なら叶うさ 夢諦めな
now it can come true, don't give up on your dreams.
Let's Try Again!
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
主役は君なのさ！
The leading role is yours!
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
夢を掴め YouTube!
Grab your dream, YouTube!
HEY!
カメラ片手に 夜空見上げよう
With a camera in hand, let's look up at the night sky,
流星群だ すぐに動画撮ろう
a meteor shower! Let's film a video right away.
君が見つけた 宇宙の美しさ
The beauty of the universe that you found,
見せてあげよう 世界中の人へ
let's show it to people all over the world.
誰しもが悩み不安 抱えているだろう
Everyone probably has worries and anxieties,
勇気を与えよう 僕らの動画で
let's give them courage with our videos.
Let's Try Again!
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
主役は君なのさ！
The leading role is yours!
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
夢を掴め YouTube!
Grab your dream, YouTube!
HEY!
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
主役は君なのさ！
The leading role is yours!
YouTube YouTube
Broadcast Yourself Yeah!
夢を掴め YouTube!
Grab your dream, YouTube!
HEY!
みんな！ありがとうー！
Everyone! Thank you so much!
仲間たちのおかげで、チャンネル登録者数も伸ばしちゃった！
Thanks to all my friends, I was able to grow my subscriber count!
こっからは、パーティだ！
From here on, it's a party!
万物も、万物も、みんなで盛り上がってけー！
Let's all get hyped together, all creation!
彼は言った　世界は必ずしもみんな平等とは限らない
He said the world is not always equal.
彼は言った　世の中には絶対勝者と敗者が存在する
He said there are absolute winners and losers in the world.
彼は言った　その勝者の頂点が自分自身そうTop of the world
He said the peak of those winners is himself—Top of the world.
彼は法であり秩序保たれる　すぐさまなくなる世界のWar
He is the law, maintaining order; the world's wars vanish instantly.
時は来た彼こそ真の支配者　彼の前にひざまずくのは敗者
The time has come, he is the true ruler; those who kneel before him are the losers.
感謝の言葉彼に乱射
Words of gratitude showered wildly upon him.
賢者識者さあかけろ拍車
Wise men and scholars, spur yourselves on.
民共崇める準備はいいか？　自分を高める運気欲しいか？
Are you people ready to worship? Do you want the luck to elevate yourselves?
さあみんな手を天にかかげ　そして今こそ祈れ
Come on, everyone, raise your hands to the sky and pray right now!
恐れるな　おののくな　吠えろ　声あげろ
Fear not, tremble not, howl, raise your voices!
その血と魂を　今ささげろ
Offer your blood and souls right now!
I'm a perfect human.
なかった　なかった　なかった　なかった　なかった　なかった
Nakata, Nakata, Nakata, Nakata...
I'm a perfect human.
We live in tokyo. なかった　なかった
We live in Tokyo. Nakata, Nakata...
I'm a perfect human.
We believe in new god　なかった　なかった
We believe in a new god. Nakata, Nakata...
I'm a perfect human.
大地パッカーン海もパッカーン　気取ってるモーゼのかようやつもパッカーン
The earth cracks open, the sea splits too—even that pretentious Moses splits open!
そんなに褒めるのやめてくれよ　ペコペコすんなよおいナポレオン
Stop praising me so much! Don't grovel, hey, Napoleon.
キングならそう歴史くつがえす　彼こそすなわちTop of the world
A king like that overturns history. He is none other than the Top of the world.
A to the T to the S to the U H to the I to the K to the O
ありがたきこの名を呼んでみよう
Let us call upon this revered name!
ATSUHIKO
Say天才！天才！
Say, genius! Genius!
まさに天才！天才！
Truly a genius! Genius!
Say天才！天才！
Say, genius! Genius!
まさに天才！天才！
Truly a genius! Genius!
Say天才！天才！もっともっと叫べー！
Say, genius! Genius! Shout more and more!
恐れるな　おののくな　吠えろ　声あげろ　その血と魂を
Fear not, tremble not, howl, raise your voices, your blood and souls...
今ささげろ
Offer them right now!
I'm a perfect human.
なかった　なかった　なかった　なかった　なかった　なかった
Nakata, Nakata, Nakata, Nakata...
I'm a perfect human.
We live in tokyo. なかった　なかった　なかった
We live in Tokyo. Nakata, Nakata...
I'm a perfect human.
We believe in new god　なかった　なかった
We believe in a new god. Nakata, Nakata...
I'm a perfect human.
なかった　なかった　なかった　なかった　なかった　なかった
Nakata, Nakata, Nakata, Nakata...
I'm a perfect human.
なかった　なかった　なかった　なかった　なかった　なかった
Nakata, Nakata, Nakata, Nakata...
I'm a perfect human.
はーちゃまちゃまー！
Haachamachama!
ワールドワイドな最高アイドル　はーちゃまこと赤井はーとでーす！
The world-wide top idol, Haachama aka Akai Haato!
はーちゃま爆誕祭2024に来てくれてありがとーーー！
Thank you for coming to Haachama's Epic Birthday Festival 2024!
というわけで、はーちゃま爆誕しましたよ！みんなどうだった？ライブ楽しめてるかー！
And so, Haachama has been born! How was it, everyone? Are you enjoying the live?
ちょっとハート落ちて…ふう…
My heart skipped a beat... phew...
あれ？あれ聞こえてる？
Huh? Can you hear me?
というわけで、SPハートでーーす！
And with that, it's SP Heart!
みんな、顔がフリーズしてポーズしてる…
Everyone, you're making that dumbfounded pose...
SPハートも爆誕しちゃいましたよ！
SP Heart has also been born!
セクシーなポーズをしておりますが、
Though I'm striking a sexy pose,
ちょっと一緒に撮影とかしちゃう？
shall we take some photos together?
はぁちゃまだってセクシーポーズできるんだからな！
Haachama can do sexy poses too, you know!
よいしょ、うぇー、どうやっ、ははははっ！
Yo-heave-ho, ugh, how do you... hahaha!
なんだ、なんだ、上から見てんだよ、まったくな！
What, what are you looking down at me for, seriously!
おらおらおらおらおらおらおらおら！
Take that, take that, take that!
はぁちゃま！おらおらおらおらおらおらおら！
Haachama! Take that, take that!
何をや、どうしてんだよ！おら！はははははっ！
What are you doing? Hey! Hahahaha!
ま、それはさておき！
Well, moving right along!
今回、「万物に愛されちゃま計画」というわけでね、ステージ、新しいステージを作ってもらいました！
This time, under the project "Haachama Loved by All Things," we had a new stage made!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
うわあ、タランチラもタランチラもあるし、信号機とかもある！
Woah, there are tarantulas and traffic lights too!
おおお、あれ、なんか、あれ、禁止テープみたいな、あははは！
Oh, wait, what's that? Like caution tape? Hahaha!
え、結構危ない感じ？ちょっとニュアンス、そういう感じ、あるじゃないの！
Eh, kinda dangerous? That kind of nuance is definitely there!
そしてそして、もちろんグッズもあるよ！
And of course, there's merchandise too!
こちら、赤井はあと誕生日記念グッズです！
Here is Akai Haato's birthday commemoration merchandise!
詳細はこちら！
Details are right here!
おおー！まずはこちら、
Oooh! First up is...
HENTシャツ！みかんさん描き下ろしのダークで悪い感じのはぁちゃまがプリントされました！
the HENT T-shirt! Featuring a dark, naughty-looking Haachama illustrated by Mikan!
文字が書いてありますね、「EVERYBODY SEXY HENTAI」って書いてあるよ！
It has text written on it, "EVERYBODY SEXY HENTAI"!
ヘンタイ！ヘンタイ！
Hentai! Hentai!
ね、ヘンタイポーズしてる？ヘンタイ、ヘンタイ？あれ、そんな、ちょっとそんなTシャツ着て、あんたヘンタイなんじゃないの、全く！ぜひ着てね！次はこちら！
See, striking a hentai pose? Hentai, hentai? Wearing a T-shirt like that, aren't you a pervert after all? Be sure to wear it! Next is this!
BAN缶バッジ！
BAN badge!
同じくみかんさん描き下ろしのTシャツのイラストが缶バッジに！
Also featuring Mikan's T-shirt illustration on a badge!
これはBAN缶バッジ！みんなもぜひこれを付けてBANされよう！BANされない、BANされる？なんでもないです。次はこちら！
This is the BAN badge! Everyone wear this and get banned! Won't get banned, will get banned? Never mind. Next is this!
フロミーズボトル！
Flomies bottle!
お風呂に入ってるはぁちゃまのデザインが入ったウォーターボトル！なんか爽やかに、の、こんなワインを片手に見たいな感じでね、転んじゃったりして
A water bottle featuring Haachama taking a bath design! Like drinking refreshingly with wine in one hand, or tripping over...
はぁちゃまのお風呂水でいろんな栄養補給しちゃう？はぁちゃまのフロミーズウォーターボトル、ぜひとも手にいれてみてね！
Replenish all kinds of nutrients with Haachama's bath water? Be sure to get your hands on Haachama's Flomies water bottle!
次は、こちらっ！
Next is this!
タランちゃまぬいぐるみ！
Tarantula-chama plushie!
まさか！夢芽ちゃんが配信で描いてくれたキャラクターがグッズ化しました！
No way! The character Mumei-chan drew on stream has been made into merchandise!
イェーイ！ありがとう夢芽ちゃん！タランちゃまなかわいいぬいぐるみだよ！
Yay! Thank you Mumei-chan! It's a cute Tarantula-chama plushie!
ぜひタランちゃまと一緒に外を歩き回ってほしいの！そして次、こちら！
I want you to walk around outside with Tarantula-chama! And next, this!
シチュエーションボイス「お風呂でもそばにいて♡」ってタイトルですけど
Situation voice titled "Be By My Side Even in the Bath ♡" is...
どうせ、またこんな、あ、そんなね、そ、あ、さっぱりしちゃってる？どんな内容なのかは購入して聴いてみてね！クレームは受け付けません！
but anyway, again like this... oh, so breezy? Find out what it's like by purchasing and listening! No complaints accepted!
次はこちら！誕生日記念フルセット！
Next is this! Birthday commemoration full set!
購入特典は直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカード！かっこいい！数量限定じゃないので、買ってくれたらみんなに直筆サイン書くよ！
Purchase bonus is a handwritten signed cheki-style bromide card! Cool! It's not limited quantity, so if you buy it, I'll write a handwritten signature for everyone!
無制限で頑張るぞ！ぜひともお買い求めよろしくお願いします！
I'll do my best limitlessly! Please purchase it!
はい！ではでは、そしてね、今日ライブやってまいりましたけども、次もまだまだライブはありますが、
Yes! Well then, and today we had a live show, but there are still more live shows to come, but
ライブが終わってからメンバーシップ限定でコールライブもやるのでみんなそこで観てね！よろしくー！
after the live, we'll also do a membership-limited call live, so everyone watch there! See you!
みんな 見てほしいの
Everyone, I want you to watch...
というわけで 赤井はあとでーす！
So, I'm Akai Haato!
さらっと告知しちゃったよー！
I just dropped a casual announcement!
BAN RTA このあと歌うよー！
I'll be singing "BAN RTA" right after this!
作詞作画ははあちゃま、編曲はハヤシベトモノリさんにお願いしました！
I asked Haachama for lyrics and art, and Hayashibe Tomonori for arrangement!
MVどうよ、ありがとう！
How's the MV? Thank you!
めちゃめちゃ最高に最高になってるから是非とも聴いてほしい！
It's turned out insanely amazing, so I definitely want you all to listen!
てかこのあと…
I mean, right after this...
歌うー！
I'll sing!
このあと本日24時に配信開始ー！
Streaming starts tonight at 24:00!
というわけでね、いやみんな、
So yeah, everyone,
ありがとうございます！
thank you so much!
最後にみんなに伝えたいことがあります！
Finally, there's something I want to tell everyone!
聞いてください、BAN RTA！
Please listen to "BAN RTA"!
欲しいなら飛び込むまで
If you wanna it dive in
待ってたって何にもならない
Nothing's gonna happen if you wait
皆さんはスリルが好きですか？
Do you all like thrills?
人生に飽き飽きしていませんか？
Aren't you get bored with life?
落ちることにも、興奮する
Even I'm excited about falling
そして儚く、美しい
That figure is aesthetics
人生どっちが良い？平和な人生とジェットコースターのような人生
Would you rather choose a life of peaceful or stormy
人生生きてる時もあるけれど
There are times in life when you fall
落ちることがないと登ることはない
But if you never fall, you won't climb
それがアトラクションだって言ってたでしょ？
You've said it's like an attraction
落ちることを恐れないで、さあ飛び込め！
Don't be afraid to fall, gonna dive in!
BAN BAN BAN BAN BA・BAN RTA
真っすぐな道を歩くだけじゃ
The straight and narrow path is not enough
物足りないでしょ？君を最強にするの、心の中で唱えて
These words will make you the strongest, chant it in your heart
魔法の言葉「HENTAI」
That's the magical word "HENTAI"
涙はいろんな種類がある、苦しみの涙や快感の涙
There are many kinds of tears, painful or pleasant
楽しすぎて気が狂いそう、こっちの方が幸せでしょ？
I think i'm going crazy, isn't it happier?
人生絶望するときもあるけれど、降ることがないと登ることはない
There's sometimes we're hopeless, you can't climb without descending
落ちるのを怖がってたら、いつまでも登れないよ
If you're scared of falling, there's no up
未来を知ることはできない、だから今に集中するの
No way i know my future, that's why focus on my feeling
私は世界一のアイドルなんだ
I'm the best idol in the world
違うお前は変態だ
(No) she said you are 'hentai'
赤信号みんなで渡れば怖くない、赤恥かいたって恥ずかしくない
When we cross the red light, that's tight, no matter how ashamed we're, it's alright
あなたは刺激を求めてる、発情してるんだからね
Are you feeling spicy? I see that you're horny
理性を捨てて刺激に身を委ねるの、そして私をセクシーにして lose my mind
Then i will be sexy and lose my mind
オーノー！止まらないこの鼓動
Oh no! I can't stop my heart beating...
ショックに飛び込むの！私狂ってるの…！
Now i'm gonna drive into shock! I am crazy about ...!
BAN BAN BAN BAN BA・BAN RTA
一緒に落ちていこう
Down down down down down together
裸を晒すことは怖くない、私たちは強いし孤独なんかじゃない
I'm not afraid to bare my soul, we can be strong and never lonely
魔法の言葉はまだかな？ NO WAY NO WAY
"Can i chant that word?" No way no way
一緒に落ちていこう
Down down down down down together
裸を晒すことは怖くない、私たちは強いし孤独なんかじゃない
I'm not afraid to bare my soul, we can be strong and never lonely
でも君は忘れてる？まだその言葉は言えないよ
Don't you miss that word? You can't say it yet
Everybody say... まだだよ！
Everybody say... Not yet!
あなたは十分興奮してる、時は来た
Aren't you feeling excited? Now that time has come
みんなで言おうぜ「変態」
Everybody say "HENTAI"